<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>UEM - Tag - Cloud Tekki</title>
        <link>https://cloudtekki.com/tags/uem/</link>
        <description>UEM - Tag - Cloud Tekki</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com (Partheeban Kandasamy (PK))</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com (Partheeban Kandasamy (PK))</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloudtekki.com/tags/uem/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Automating Windows 10 VM build auto enrolled into UEM using Packer</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/packer-windows/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/packer-windows/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In this post, I&rsquo;ll be covering how you can automate the process of building a Windows 10 images on your Lab. As a part of my daily job working with Workspace ONE Unified Endpoint Management, I work with a lot of Modern Management use cases and this requires testing various use cases on various versions of Windows 10. To always start with a clean image, I use Packer to build and enroll the device for me into my lab UEM tenant thus speeding up the process and reducing the probability for errors.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Unpacking Organization Groups in Workspace ONE UEM</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/uem-organization-groups/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/uem-organization-groups/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What are Organization Groups in Workspace One UEM?
What are the best practices with how to set Organization Groups up for our use case?
Can we insert an OG between OGs? Do we have the right setup?
These are very common questions on Organization Groups which is a very foundational element within Workspace ONE UEM. Over the several years of working with Workspace ONE UEM (formerly AirWatch), no one has tried to provide a complete picture of what an Organization Group is.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
