<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>EUC - Category - Cloud Tekki</title>
        <link>https://cloudtekki.com/categories/euc/</link>
        <description>EUC - Category - Cloud Tekki</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com (Partheeban Kandasamy (PK))</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com (Partheeban Kandasamy (PK))</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloudtekki.com/categories/euc/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Edge Services Observability for Unified Access Gateway</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/eso/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/eso/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Edge Services Observability" Edge Services Observability  Unified Access Gateway (UAG) is a key component in most VMware End User Computing deployments, including Workspace ONE and Horizon. The UAG hosts various Edge Services like VMware Tunnel, Content Gateway, Secure Email Gateway, Reverse Proxy and Horizon Secure (External) Access. Additionally, the UAG can also provide DMZ Authentication and Identity Bridging. These services play a pivotal role in providing Zero Trust Network Access to corporate resources.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>An Intro to Workspace ONE Hub Templates</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/hub-templates/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/hub-templates/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hi! I&rsquo;m Nagul Subramanian working on VMware End User Computing technologies for more than 7 years and have gained a lot of field experience on WS ONE and Mobility. I&rsquo;ve always had a personal goal to contribute my knowledge back to the community. As I explored ways to do that, I ran into PK and Cloud Tekki. This is my first blog post(hopefully first of many) and would love to hear your feedback!]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Creating a Custom Connector in WS1 Intelligence</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/intel-custom-connector/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/intel-custom-connector/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is Workspace ONE Intelligence? Workspace ONE Intelligence is the mainstream data analytics product within the Workspace ONE product suite. It allows you to tap into a wide array of data sources (from UEM, SDK enabled apps, Access and others) to get unique Insights &amp; Automation capabilities over your End User Computing landscape!
Features  Unified Visibility: Workspace ONE Intelligence aggregates and correlates device, application and user data together in one place to deliver a complete view of the entire digital workspace environment.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Update 1: Migration tool for WS1 Access</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/access-migration-u1/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/access-migration-u1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This is a quick post covering an exciting update to the Workspace ONE Access Migration Tool. If you are interested in learning more about the tool, please check out these resources -
 Why was this Migration tool built? How can you use it? Download the Migration tool  Access Migration Tool - Logo" Access Migration Tool - Logo  As a quick recap, the fling allows easy migration of Apps (excluding virtual apps) from one WS1 Access tenant to another (both on-prem to SaaS as well as SaaS to SaaS) by preserving the user experience as much as possible while reducing the migration effort by automating these major tasks -]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Fling: Migration tool for WS1 Access</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/access-migration/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 23:58:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/access-migration/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Migration?&hellip;Migraine?&hellip; When it comes to migration scenarios, the most involved and difficult migration within the EUC lineup (that I can think of) is the WS1 Access tenant migration. It is equivalent to adopting a new IDP solution as you&rsquo;ll have to re-federate all the apps in order to successfully complete a migration.
And this is case regardless of where you are trying to move from -
On-Premise to SaaS  As Cloud is picking up steam and as features are developed with a cloud-first mentality, tt makes sense to offload the management of the Access Service to VMware This scenario is also getting more common as Access and Hub Services are FedRAMP certified as of CY Q4 2020  SaaS to SaaS  This is a not very common use case but few situations demand them nonetheless predominantly due to issues arising from high customization entertained early in the product adoption lifecycle Another use case for is populating a UAT or a DEV tenant with Apps from another tenant   Path to Migration First and foremost, a migration is possible as documented in @williamsmt blog which provides a detailed walk through of the entire migration approach.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Automating Windows 10 VM build auto enrolled into UEM using Packer</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/packer-windows/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/packer-windows/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In this post, I&rsquo;ll be covering how you can automate the process of building a Windows 10 images on your Lab. As a part of my daily job working with Workspace ONE Unified Endpoint Management, I work with a lot of Modern Management use cases and this requires testing various use cases on various versions of Windows 10. To always start with a clean image, I use Packer to build and enroll the device for me into my lab UEM tenant thus speeding up the process and reducing the probability for errors.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Unpacking Organization Groups in Workspace ONE UEM</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/uem-organization-groups/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/uem-organization-groups/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What are Organization Groups in Workspace One UEM?
What are the best practices with how to set Organization Groups up for our use case?
Can we insert an OG between OGs? Do we have the right setup?
These are very common questions on Organization Groups which is a very foundational element within Workspace ONE UEM. Over the several years of working with Workspace ONE UEM (formerly AirWatch), no one has tried to provide a complete picture of what an Organization Group is.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Access: The tale of the hidden APIs</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/access-apis/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/access-apis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Evolving Access through APIs Workspace One Access is VMware&rsquo;s Product Line that helps provide seamless single sign on and conditional access for Applications from End User&rsquo;s client devices. It is built using technologies such as
 SAML (RFC 7522) OAuth (RFC 6749) and Open ID Connect  If you are new to the Product, you can find more details about WorkspaceONE(WS1) Access
 Product Page - here Documentation - here  In this post, I&rsquo;m going to cover a neat trick that will help you find and build on the APIs that are available with WS1 Access.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
