<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>EUC - Category - Cloud Tekki</title>
        <link>https://cloudtekki.com/categories/euc/</link>
        <description>EUC - Category - Cloud Tekki</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com (Partheeban Kandasamy (PK))</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com (Partheeban Kandasamy (PK))</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloudtekki.com/categories/euc/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Unpacking Organization Groups in Workspace ONE UEM</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/uem-organization-groups/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/uem-organization-groups/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What are Organization Groups in Workspace One UEM?
What are the best practices with how to set Organization Groups up for our use case?
Can we insert an OG between OGs? Do we have the right setup?
These are very common questions on Organization Groups which is a very foundational element within Workspace ONE UEM. Over the several years of working with Workspace ONE UEM (formerly AirWatch), no one has tried to provide a complete picture of what an Organization Group is.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Access: The tale of the hidden APIs</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/access-apis/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/access-apis/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Evolving Access through APIs Workspace One Access is VMware&rsquo;s Product Line that helps provide seamless single sign on and conditional access for Applications from End User&rsquo;s client devices. It is built using technologies such as
 SAML (RFC 7522) OAuth (RFC 6749) and Open ID Connect  If you are new to the Product, you can find more details about WorkspaceONE(WS1) Access
 Product Page - here Documentation - here  In this post, I&rsquo;m going to cover a neat trick that will help you find and build on the APIs that are available with WS1 Access.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
