<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Automation - Tag - Cloud Tekki</title>
        <link>https://cloudtekki.com/tags/automation/</link>
        <description>Automation - Tag - Cloud Tekki</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com (Partheeban Kandasamy (PK))</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com (Partheeban Kandasamy (PK))</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloudtekki.com/tags/automation/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Automating Windows 10 VM build auto enrolled into UEM using Packer</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/packer-windows/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/packer-windows/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In this post, I&rsquo;ll be covering how you can automate the process of building a Windows 10 images on your Lab. As a part of my daily job working with Workspace ONE Unified Endpoint Management, I work with a lot of Modern Management use cases and this requires testing various use cases on various versions of Windows 10. To always start with a clean image, I use Packer to build and enroll the device for me into my lab UEM tenant thus speeding up the process and reducing the probability for errors.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Beginner&#39;s Guide: Bootstrapping kubernetes on Ubuntu 20.04 using kubeadm w/ Calico</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/bootstrap-k8s/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/bootstrap-k8s/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This is not going to be an eye-opening new post about bootstrapping Kubernetes - a lot of people have done it and several blog posts already exists. I&rsquo;m hoping to capture the information here to serve as an easy documentation for myself and other beginners in the area of Kubernetes and Cloud Native
Getting Started As a baseline, here are my assumptions about those following along or to my future self]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
