<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Cloud Tekki</title>
        <link>https://cloudtekki.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Cloud Tekki</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com (Partheeban Kandasamy (PK))</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com (Partheeban Kandasamy (PK))</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloudtekki.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Being a Trusted Advisor</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/trusted-advisor/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/trusted-advisor/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;ve spent close to a decade working with Customers and this blog post aims to summarize my most valuable learnings from working closely with Customers in the hopes that it will help others with their Customer Relationship Management!
My entire customer experience can be summed up as - &ldquo;Working with the top tier Customers who need strategic, tactical and technical guidance on utilizing VMware Products effectively and achieving their Business Objectives!]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>The Top 5 IT Team Challenges</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/it-team-challenges/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/it-team-challenges/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;ve spent close to a decade working with Customers and this blog post aims to summarize my most valuable learnings from working closely with Customers in the hopes that it will help others with their Customer Relationship Management!
My time with the Customers gave me a front row seat to various IT teams ranging from those that consider themselves inadequate (⚠️ SPOILER ALERT! ALMOST everyone thinks/knows that they have some issue - organizational silos, lack expertise, lack leadership, lack discipline or lack organization skills.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Summing up Chapter 4, My Field Experiences</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/field-lessons/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/field-lessons/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/img/misc/time-cx/stones.jpeg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>I&rsquo;ve just crossed the 90 day mark on my recent Product Management stint with the Employee Experience team with Workspace ONE. As I get comfortable with the role, I&rsquo;ve come to realize that in this role I feel like I&rsquo;m thriving, adding value and making the most impact! These days, I am excited to get out of bed and I have trouble sleeping because I&rsquo;m already excited about what I can accomplish the next day!]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Registered mode w/ a focus on Windows 10</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/registered-mode/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/registered-mode/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/img/euc/registered-mode/hero.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Registered mode is a capability in UEM that allows IT to deliver a secure way for Employees to access corporate data using Workspace ONE without having to manage their devices. While the core philosophy behind Registered mode is the same across different platforms, the problem it addresses on various platforms are slightly different. Understanding its origin will shed some light into how you can effectively utilize this capability and provide seamless access to your Employees Evolution of Registered Mode As a technologist that&rsquo;s been following and absorbing all the progress that&rsquo;s been happening this space, I wanted to start this post by covering the evolution of Registered Mode with Workspace ONE over the last 4-5 years.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Welcome to the Flip Side</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/the-flip-side/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/the-flip-side/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Having changed roles (or at least titles) almost once every year (TAM@2014➔SAM@2016➔TSM@2017➔TAM Lead@2018➔CSM@2019➔CSA@2020), I don&rsquo;t usually make a huge deal about role changes but this is a major pivot ending a 7 year long chapter in my career and thus an exception.
Bitter sweet moment as this minute will mark the end of a 7 year long chapter in my career.
&mdash; Partheeban Kandasamy (PK) (@pkblah) July 17, 2021  Over the last 7 years, I&rsquo;ve had the incredible opportunity to work with large Enterprises, form great relationships and helped several meet their digital transformation goals.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Securing Outlook from Unmanaged Devices with Tunnel</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/tunnel-o365-conditional-access/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/tunnel-o365-conditional-access/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Howdy! I&rsquo;m Kevin Ten Eyck, a Staff EUC Customer Success Architect at VMware. I&rsquo;ve been with VMware for 4 years and greatly enjoy all things EUC! Coming from a background in Mobility and VDI, I love finding new challenges to be solved. Would love to hear your feedback or alternate ideas on how you&rsquo;ve solved similar problems!
What problem does this solve? This blog post is targeted at Workspace ONE UEM administrators who are being asked to prevent unmanaged devices from accessing Office 365 applications.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Edge Services Observability for Unified Access Gateway</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/eso/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/eso/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Edge Services Observability" Edge Services Observability  Unified Access Gateway (UAG) is a key component in most VMware End User Computing deployments, including Workspace ONE and Horizon. The UAG hosts various Edge Services like VMware Tunnel, Content Gateway, Secure Email Gateway, Reverse Proxy and Horizon Secure (External) Access. Additionally, the UAG can also provide DMZ Authentication and Identity Bridging. These services play a pivotal role in providing Zero Trust Network Access to corporate resources.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>An Intro to Workspace ONE Hub Templates</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/hub-templates/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/hub-templates/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hi! I&rsquo;m Nagul Subramanian working on VMware End User Computing technologies for more than 7 years and have gained a lot of field experience on WS ONE and Mobility. I&rsquo;ve always had a personal goal to contribute my knowledge back to the community. As I explored ways to do that, I ran into PK and Cloud Tekki. This is my first blog post(hopefully first of many) and would love to hear your feedback!]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Creating a Custom Connector in WS1 Intelligence</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/intel-custom-connector/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/intel-custom-connector/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is Workspace ONE Intelligence? Workspace ONE Intelligence is the mainstream data analytics product within the Workspace ONE product suite. It allows you to tap into a wide array of data sources (from UEM, SDK enabled apps, Access and others) to get unique Insights &amp; Automation capabilities over your End User Computing landscape!
Features  Unified Visibility: Workspace ONE Intelligence aggregates and correlates device, application and user data together in one place to deliver a complete view of the entire digital workspace environment.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Update 1: Migration tool for WS1 Access</title>
    <link>https://cloudtekki.com/post/access-migration-u1/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>partheeban.kandasamy@gmail.com</author>
    <guid>https://cloudtekki.com/post/access-migration-u1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This is a quick post covering an exciting update to the Workspace ONE Access Migration Tool. If you are interested in learning more about the tool, please check out these resources -
 Why was this Migration tool built? How can you use it? Download the Migration tool  Access Migration Tool - Logo" Access Migration Tool - Logo  As a quick recap, the fling allows easy migration of Apps (excluding virtual apps) from one WS1 Access tenant to another (both on-prem to SaaS as well as SaaS to SaaS) by preserving the user experience as much as possible while reducing the migration effort by automating these major tasks -]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
